Ada pertanyaan untuk pasangan calon nomor 4
yang akan dibalas oleh untuk pasang calon nomor lainnya.
Pertanyaan untuk nomor 4
Banyak terjadi kasus korupsi dan para kepala daerah menjadi tersangka kasus korupsi,
KPK Telah menangkap sejumlah kepala daerah yang ikut pilkada tahun ini
ada juga kepala daerah dari jawa barat.
Move or die.
DEADPOOL: Pump
the hate brakes, Thanos.
I ain't lettin' Cable
get to him,
but I can't do this alone.
We need backup.
We're gonna form
a super-duper fucking group.
It's time to get back
on LinkedIn.
Meet Bedlam.
My name's Shatterstar.
Domino.
-I'm lucky.
-(COCKS GUN AND FIRES)
DEADPOOL:
Luck isn't a superpower.
And certainly
not very cinematic.
-Yes, it is.
-DEADPOOL: Let's meet
in the middle
and say "No, it isn't."
Fuck it. It's showtime.
Whoo!
CABLE: You're no fucking hero.
You're just a clown,
dressed up as a sex toy.
So dark.
You sure you're not
from the DC Universe?
DEADPOOL: Bring it on,
One-Eyed Willie.
Your bullets,
they're really fast!
Last but not least...
Peter.
DEADPOOL: Any power
you wanna tell us about?
I don't... I don't have one.
Um, I just saw the ad.
DEADPOOL: You're in.